Guide to the Marilyn Symmes Collection of Art Exhibition Ephemera 1973-2019 (bulk 1990s-2019) PR 352
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Single Artist Exhibitions, 1973-2019 (bulk 1990s-2019)
  - T (Set 2), 1982-2019 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 3)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Barbara Takenaga, Al Taylor, Paul Taylor, Joyce Tenneson, Wayne Thiebaud, Hank Willis Thomas, Mildred Thompson, Lin Tianmiao, Louis Comfort Tiffany, Mark Tobey, George Tooker, John Torreano, James Turrell, and Richard Tuttle. Also includes a MOMA brochure on its 1988 exhibition, "Projects: Rosemarie Trockel" with a short biography of the artist. Includes a 1994 MOMA brochure on its exhibition, "Cy Twombly: A Retrospective"; a 2001 National Gallery of Art brochure on its exhibition, "Cy Twombly: The Sculpture" and a 2018 Gagrosian booklet on its exhibition, "Cy Twombly: In Beauty it is finished".
  - U, 1993-2015 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 6)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Lee Ufan and Tom Uttech. Also includes a prospectus for "A Day in the Bleachers" by Arnold Hano and illustrated by Mark Ulriksen.
  - U (Set 2), 2009-2018 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 4)
    Includes material for artists, including, Lee Ufan and Tom Uttech.
  - V, 1994-2016 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 7)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Manolo Valdes, James Valerio, Sara VanDerBeek, Francesco Vezzoli, and Bill Viola. Also includes a Whitney Museum 2010 exhibition guide for Sara VanDerBeek, a Museum of Contemporary Art, Cleveland, 2014 interview with Sara VanDerBeek, a Gagosian Gallery, Beverly Hills, and a Guggenheim Museum 2002 exhibition guide for Bill Viola: Going Forth by Day.
  - V (Set 2), 1994-2019 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 5)
    Includes material for artists, including, Tony Vaccaro, Manolo Valdes, Julio Valdez, and Leo Villareal. Also includes a 2011 Parrish Art Museum program brochure on its exhibition, "Esteban Vicente: Portrait of the Artist" with a short biography of the artist.
  - Wa, 1993-2016 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 1)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Edmund De Waal, John Walker, Richard Walker, Darren Waterston, and Carleton E. Watkins. Also includes a Kraushaar Gallery 2005 exhibition pamphlet Lee Walton: Baseball Drawings, a Philadelphia Museum of Art exhibition guide Marcel Wanders: Daydreams, and a Massachusetts Museum of Contemporary Art 2014 exhibition pamphlet Darren Waterston: Uncertain Beauty.
  - Warhol, Andy, 1994-2014 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 2)
    Includes material for artist Andy Warhol, including a DIA Center for the Arts 1994 exhibition guide for Andy Warhol: The Last Supper Paintings, a prospectus for a limited edition portfolio of photographs of Andy Warhol taken by William John Kennedy in 1964, and a MoMA 2003 exhibition guide for Andy Warhol: Screen Tests.
  - We-Wel, 1993-2016 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 3)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, William Wegman, Lawrence Weiner, Robert Weingarten, and Ai WeiWei. Also includes a Whitney Museum 2007 exhibition guide for Lawrence Weiner: As Far As The Eye Can See, a Kentler International Drawing Space 2006 exhibition pamphlet for Monika Weiss: Limen 2, and a Zimmerli Art Museum 2012 exhibition guide for Rachel Perry Welty: 24/7.
  - Welliver, Neil, 1995-2015 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 4)
    Includes material for artists, Neil Welliver, including a Alexandre Gallery 2004 exhibition catalogue for Neil Welliver: Oil Studies.
  - Wen-Whi, 1992-2015 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 5)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Franz West, Minor White, and Rachel Whiteread. Also includes a Hall Art Foundation 2014 exhibition guide for Franz West: Les Pommes d'Adam, and a Clark Art Institute 1998 exhibition guide for Charles White: Progression of the American Negro.
  - Wi, 2001-2016 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 6)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Charmion Von Wiegand, Kehinde Wiley, Christopher Williams, Philemona Williamson, Fred Wilson, and Jane Wilson. Also includes a Brooklyn Museum 2015 media preview for Kehinde Wiley: A New Republic, a MoMA 2014 exhibition guide for Christopher Williams: The Production Line of Happiness, and a Ubu Gallery 2006 publication for Stanislaw Ignacy Witkiewicz: Drawings from the 1930s, and a 2013 mailing from Michael Rosenfeld Gallery that included, with Wiegand. a large lapel pin for the exhibition American Abstraction.
  - Winters, Terry, 1999-2003 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 1)
    Includes material for artist Terry Winters, including a Two Palms Press 2002 publication for Terry Winters: Shadowgraphs.
  - Wo-Wy, 1997-2016 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 2)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, Jonas Wood, Betty Woodman, Francesca Woodman, Christopher Wool, Alexi Worth, Frank Lloyd Wright, and Richard Wright. Also includes a New Museum of Contemporary Art 1998 exhibition guide for Sweet Oblivion: The Urban Landscape of Martin Wong, a Marian Goodman Gallery 2012 publication for Francesca Woodman: The Blueprints, and a National Building Museum 1997 exhibition guide for Frank Lloyd Wright: American Spirit Alive in Japan.
  - W (Set 2) (2 folders), 1992-2019 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 6-7)
    Includes material for artists, including, among others, John Walker, S.B. Walker, Kay WalkingStick, Andy Warhol, Darren Waterston, William Wegman, James Welling, Rebecca Welz, Richard Wentworth, Stephen Westfall, Clarence White, Robert Whitman, Richard Wilcox, Philomenia Williamson, Christopher Wilmarth, Fred Wilson, and Jane Wilson. Also includes a 2002 Smithsonian Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden brochure on its H.C. Westermann exhibition with a short biography of the artist. Includes a 2018 exhibition brochure on the David Hammons curated exhibition, "Charles White/ Leonardo Da Vinci" with a short biography of Charles White. Includes a 2014 MOMA Program brochure on the exhibition, "Christopher Williams: The Production Line of Happiness". Includes a 2009 Kentler International Drawing Space brochure on its exhibition, "Hugh Williams: Alabama Wire Drawings" with a short biography of the artist. Includes a 2018 Michael Rosenfeld Gallery booklet that features selections from William T. Williams' 111 1/2 Series. Includes a Van Cleef & Arpels booklet on its installation, "Noah's Ark inspires Van Cleef & Arpels: Concept & Design Robert Wilson" with a short biography on Robert Wilson. Includes a 2018 Drawing Center brochure on its exhibition, "Terry Winters: Facts and Fictions" with a short biography of the artist.
  - X, 2013-2016 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 3)
    Includes material for artists Liu Xiaodong, Qiu Xiaofei, and Xiaoze Xie.
  - Y, 2003-2015 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 4)
    Includes material for artists, Mao Yan, Catherine Yass, Liu Ye, David Zink Yi, Aaron Young, Jack Youngerman, Lisa Yuskavage, and Kimiko Yoshida.
  - Z, 1994-2016 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 5)
    Includes material for artists Abbie Zabar, Robert Zandvliet, Zao Wou-Ki, Eva Zeisel, Alexander Zhitomirsky, Elyn Zimmerman, Nola Zirin, Andrea Zittel, Marilyn Zorach, Gilberto Zorio, Kevin Zucker, and Unica Zurn. Also includes a New Museum 2006 exhibition guide for Andrea Zittel: Critical Space, and 2012 press releases from the Andrea Rosen Gallery for Andrea Zittel's Fluid Panel State.
  - X,Y,Z (Set 2), 2009-2018 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 8)
    Includes material for artists, including, Zhang Xiaogang, Lisa Yuskavage, Qi Zhilong, and Nola Zirin.
  - Oversize (1 of 3 folders), 1994-2016 (Folder FF-2)
    Includes advertisement poster for artist's proofs of Donald Baechler's Red Coral (2004); Gabrielle Basilico (2004) at MIT galleries; Dan Colen Secrets and Cymbals, Smoke and Scissors (My Friend Dash's Wall in the Future) (2006) at Deitch Projects; Dan Colen Blowin' in the Wind (2012) at Gagosian; Gregory Crewdson Sanctuary (2011) at Gagosian Rome; newspaper format guide for Ann Hamilton the event of a thread (2012) at Park Avenue Armory; Tim Hawkinson (2009) at Pace/Wildenstein; Jasper Johns Catenary (2005) at Matthew Marks; Joe Bradley Krasdale (2016) at Gagosian; Roy Lichtenstein Nudes (1994) at Leo Castelli; Agnes Martin The '80s: Grey Paintings (2011) at 534 West 25th Street; Steven Parrino (2007) at Gagosian; A.R. Penck Constructions (2004) at Michael Werner; Charles Seliger New Paintings (2006) at Michael Rosenfeld; Richard Serra To Whom It May Concern (1995) at Matthew Marks; Richard Serra Venice Notebook Series (2002) at Gemini; Christer Stromholm (2016) at Pace/MacGill; Thomas Struth (2015) at the Met; Robert Therrien (2008) at Gagosian; prospectus (2000) for book Phrase Book by Rick Moody, illustrated by Fred Tomaselli; Andy Warhol From the Sonnabend Collection (2009) at Gagosian.
  - Oversize (2 of 3 folders), 2004-2014 (Folder FF-3)
    Includes John Baldasarre (2005), Noses & Ears (2006), Sediment (Part 2) (2010), Double Play (2012), and Movie Scripts/Art (no year) at Marian Goodman; Glenn Brown (2014) at Gagosian; Aaron Curry mmnktlplkt (2010) at Michael Werner; Jim Dine (2004) at Pace Prints; Peter Doig New Paintings (2009) at Michael Werner; Felix Gonzalez-Torres (2004) at Max Fraenkel; Al Held (2004) at Robert Miller; Christopher Wool (2006) at Gagosian Los Angeles.
  - Oversize (3 of 3 folders), 1995-2015 (Folder FF-4)
    Includes Lothar Baumgarten Imago Mundi (2004) at Marian Goodman; Dan Colen Miracle Paintings (2014) at Gagosian; Anselm Kiefer hortus philosophorum (2009) and Next Year in Jerusalem (2010) at Gagosian; Ryan McGinness Figure Drawings (2014) at Pace Prints; Philip Pearlstein (2004) at Robert Miller; Giuseppe Penone (2012) at Gagosian; Robert Rauschenberg Works on Metal (2014) at Gagosian; Edward Ruscha Anamorphic Paintings (1995) at Leo Castelli; Richard Serra (2009) at Gagosian; Francesco Vezzoli The Gore Vidal Trilogy (2006); Adrian Villar Rojas Two Suns (2015) at Marian Goodman; Lawrence Weiner En Route (2005), At the Level of the Sea (2009), and Gyroscopically Speaking (2011) at Marian Goodman.
  - Oversize (Set 2), 1980, 2007-2018 (Folder FF-5)
    Includes: "The Feminist Future" symposium at MoMA, 2 posters (2007); Creative Time: Playing the Building Installation by David Byrne (2008); "Great Power" by Martha Rosler at Mitchell-Innes & Nash (2008); "Agitprop!" by Martha Rosler at Mitchell-Innes & Nash (2015-16); "Inherent Innate Tension" by Lawrence Weiner at Marian Goodman Gallery, 2 posters (2017); "Evolution" by Michal Rovner (2018); "Bialo-Czerivona" by Piotr Uklanski at Gagosian (2008); "Pollock/Benton" by John Baldassari at Marian Goodman (2016); "Miro and Life in General" by John Baldassari at Marian Goodman (2017); Duke Riley at Magnan Metz Gallery (2017); Christopher Wool at Gagosian (2010); "New Capri, Capri, Free Capri" by Mark Grotjahn at Gagosian (2018); Jonas Wood at Anton Kern Gallery (2013); "Equals" by Richard Serra at Gemini G.E.L., 2 posters (2018); Ansel Adams at Detroit Institute of Arts (1980).
- Series II. Two Artists Exhibitions, 1994, 2000-2016
  The series includes announcements, guides, brochures, checklists, artwork images, and posters from galleries, dealers and museums related to exhibitions centered on the work of two artists. There are approximately 65 documents in the series by the donor's count. The container list includes reference to all the exhibitions represented in the series, identifying them by artist surnames in the form "artist 1/artist 2."
  The series is arranged alphabetically by the surname of the first artist used in the publicity material, retaining the order as presented by the collector/donor. One oversize item was flattened and stored separately, and is noted at the end of the container list. The entry in the container list that refers to "Set 2" holds the items received from Symmes in 2019 and that were boxed apart from the earlier 2016 accession.
  - A-C, 1994, 2004-2016 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 6)
    Includes material for artists Adamo/Castle, Albers/Albers, Albers/Judd, Allora/Calzadilla, Anderson/Low, Andrews/Israel, Apfelbaum/Giorno, Arbus/Nolan, Bailey/Hirst, Bearden/Lewis, Becher/Sander, Bertozzi/Casoni, Beuys/Le Va, Blume/Blume, Boetti/Bouabre, Bond/Simon, Byington/Nakadate, Calder/Prouve, Cardiff/Bures, Cattelan/Fontana, Chamberlain/Francis, and Chamberlain/Prouve.
  - D-K, 2006-2016 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 7)
    Includes material for artists Donovan/Mangold, Dubuffet/Basquiat, Eilshemius/Thompson, Fekete/Schiel, Fischli/Weiss, Flavin/Albers, Friedlander/Bonnard, Giacometti/Bacon, Giacometti/Klein, Graham/Vogt, Guston/Johns, Inez/Vinoodh, Israel/Ellis, Jacquette/Burckhardt, and Johns/Nauman.
  - L-Z, 2000-2016 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 8)
    Includes material for artists Lawrence/Knight, Le Corbusier/Jeanneret, Lundeberg/Feitelson, McCartney/McCartney, Nauman/Rothenberg, Oldenburg/Van Bruggen, Picasso/Braque, Rich/Grossman, Richter/Pardo, Robbins/Becher, Sagmeister/Walsh, Sargent/Bingham, Sayler/Morris, Shinzo/Fukuhara, Von Graevenitz/Morellet, Weiner/Young, Wilson/Ryman, Winokur/Burko, Witkin/Witkin, and Wood/Kusaka.
  - A-Z (Set 2), 2001-2018 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 9)
    Includes material for artists, including, Vito Acconci/Ana Mendieta, Huma Bhabha/Matthew Day Jackson, Alexander Calder/Joan Miro, Nicole Eisenman/Andy Warhol, Jose Manuel Fors/Rogelio Lopez-Marin (Gory), Jim Fricke/Charlie Ahearn, Bill Jacobson/Richard Artschwager, Yvonne Jacquette/Rudy Burckhardt, Kathe Kollwitz/Sue Coe, Agnes Martin/Richard Tuttle, Andrea Robbins/Max Becher, and Julia Weist/Nestor Sire,
  - Warhol/Basquiat, 2002 (Offsite-box 22, Item 3)
    Poster for exhibition at Gagosian Gallery, still rolled in original clear plastic mailing tube.
  - Oversize, 2013 (Folder FF-1)
    Includes only one poster: Halley/Mendini at Mary Boone Gallery.
- Series III. Multiple Artists Exhibitions, 1992-2016
  The series includes announcements, guides, brochures, checklists, artwork images, and posters from galleries, dealers and museums related to exhibitions that included work by more than two artists. Generally, these exhibitions emphasized topics, genre, or other themes, rather than highlighting particular artists. Unlike the first two series, which identified artist names, the container list here identifies all the galleries or museums that presented exhibitions represented in the series. (Although the degree of overlap is not known, the institutions identified here are representative of those found in the first two series.) By the donor's count, there are approximately 500 items in the series.
  The series is arranged in alphabetical order, by institution name. There was no original order to the documents in this series so the arrangement was determined by the processing archivist. A few oversize items were flattened and stored separately, and they are noted at the end of the container list. The entry in the container list that refers to "Set 2" holds the items received from Symmes in 2019 and that were boxed apart from the earlier 2016 accession.
  - 292 Gallery, 1994 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 1)
  - A, 2003-2015 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 2)
    Includes material from multiple artists shows at the following museums and galleries: Alexandre Gallery, Aljira Center, American Academy of Arts and Letters, American Folk Art Museum, Anthony Grant, The Art Students League of New York, and Axa Gallery.
  - B, 1995-2016 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 3)
    Includes material from multiple artists shows at the following museums and galleries: The Bard Graduate Center, Beach Museum of Art at Kansas State University, The Berkeley Art Museum at University of California, Bernard Goldberg Fine Arts, Bernard Toale Gallery, Betty Cunningham Gallery, Betty Krulik Fine Art, Ltd, The Boston Athenaeum, The Brodsky Center, The Bronx Council on the Arts, and The Brooklyn Museum.
  - C-D, 2000-2016 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 4)
    Includes material from multiple artists shows at the following museums and galleries: Cantor Arts Center at Stanford University, Cencebaugh Contemporary Gallery, The Chelsea Art Museum, Cook Fine Art, Davison Art Center at Wesleyan University, DC Moore Gallery, Dominique Levy Gallery, Dorsky Gallery, and The Drawing Center.
  - David Findlay Jr. Gallery, 2006-2016 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 5)
    Includes material from multiple artists shows at the David Findlay Jr. Gallery.
  - Deitch Projects, 2002-2008 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 6)
    Includes material from multiple artists shows at Deitch Projects.
  - E-F, 1992-2015 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 7)
    Includes material from multiple artists shows at the following museums and galleries: EFA Gallery, ExitArt, Eyebeam, The Fabric Workshop and Museum, FiveMyles Gallery, F.I.T. Museum, Flatlanders Art Galleries, The Fraenkel Gallery, The Frances Lehman Loeb Art Center at Vassar College, and the Franklin Furnace Archives.
  - A-F (Set 2), 1988-2018 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 10)
    Includes material from multiple artists shows at the following museums and galleries: A/D Gallery (1990), The Armory Show (2014), Bedford Gallery at Lesher Center, Center for Maine Contemporary Art, Cook Fine Art, Craig F. Starr Associates, David Findlay Jr. Gallery, DC Moore Gallery, Deitch Projects (Studios), Diane Brown Gallery (1988), and FiveMyles.
  - G-H, 2002-2016 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 8)
    Includes material from multiple artists shows at the following museums and galleries: Galerie St. Etienne, Gemini G.E.L., The Getty Center, Gitterman Gallery, Greenberg Van Doren Gallery, The Grey Art Gallery at N.Y.U., The Grolier Club, Hafnarborg Gallery, Hauser & Wirth Gallery, Hirschl & Adler Galleries, and the Hebrew Union College.
  - Gagosian Galleries, 2005-2016 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 1)
    Includes material from multiple artists shows at Gagosian Galleries.
  - I, 2006-2016 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 2)
    Includes material from multiple artists shows at the following museums and galleries: Institute for Women and Art at Rutgers University, International Center of Photography, and International Print Center New York.
  - J-K, 1998-2015 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 3)
    Includes material from multiple artists shows at the following museums and galleries: Jack Rutberg Fine Arts, James Cohan Gallery, Japan Society, Jeannie Freilich Contemporary Gallery, The Jewish Museum, John Gibson Gallery, June Kelly Gallery, Karen McCready Fine Art, Katharina Rich Perlow Gallery, Kentler International Drawing Space, and Keith De Lellis.
  - G-K (Set 2), 2001-2019 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 11)
    Includes material from multiple artists shows at the following museums and galleries: Gagrosian Gallery, The Galerie St. Etienne, Gemini G.E.L., The J. Paul Getty Museum, Grey Art Gallery NYU, Hirschl & Adler Galleries, Inc. (2001), Howard Greenberg Gallery, International Center of Photography Museum, International Print Center New York, Jack Rutberg Fine Arts, June Kelly Gallery, and Kentler International Drawing Space
  - L-M, 1992-2016 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 4)
    Includes material from multiple artists shows at the following museums and galleries: Larissa Goldston Gallery, Laurence Miller Gallery, Leslie Tonkontow Artworks & Projects, Library of Congress, Loretta Howard Gallery, The Louvre Museum, Luhring Augustine Gallery, The Museum of Art and Design, Margarete Roeder Gallery, Marianne Elrick-Manley Gallery, Mary Boone Gallery, Mary Ryan Gallery, MassMOCA, Matthew Marks Gallery, Michael Werner Gallery, Mitchell-Innes & Nash Gallery, MOCA, The Morgan Library & Museum, Musee D'Art Americain Giverny, Museo del Barrio, Museum of the City of New York, Museum of Fine Arts Boston, and Museum of Jewish Heritage. Also includes a mailing of documentary film releases by Michael Blackwood Productions.
  - Marian Goodman Gallery, Marlborough Gallery, Michael Rosenfeld Gallery, 1994-2016 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 5)
    Includes material from multiple artists shows at Marian Goodman Gallery, Marlborough Gallery, and Michael Rosenfeld Gallery.
  - The Metropolitan Museum of Art and Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), 1995-2016 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 6)
    Includes material from multiple artists shows from The Met and MoMA.
  - N, 1995-2016 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 1)
    Includes material from multiple artists shows at the following museums and galleries: National Academy Museum and School, National Building Museum, National Museum of Women in the Arts, The Newark Museum, The New Jersey State Museum, The New Museum, the City of New York Parks and Recreation, New York Public Libraries, The Noguchi Museum, and The Nolan/Eckman Gallery.
  - P, 2003-2016 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 2)
    Includes material from multiple artists shows at the following museums and galleries: The Pace Gallery, Pace/Wildenstein Gallery, The Park Avenue Armory, The Parrish Art Museum, Paula Cooper Gallery, Peter Freeman, Inc., The Philadelphia Museum of Art, and The Planthouse Gallery.
  - R, 2000-2015 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 3)
    Includes material from multiple artists shows at the following museums and galleries: Ransom Gallery at University of Texas (Austin), Ricco/Maresca Gallery, Robert Mann Gallery, Robert Miller Gallery, The Rutgers Center for Innovative Print and Paper, and Ruth Chandler Williamson Gallery.
  - L-R (Set 2), 1988, 1989, 1992, 1994, 2002-2019 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 12)
    Includes material from multiple artists shows at the following museums and galleries: The LeWitt Collection, Marian Goodman Gallery, The Met, Michael Rosenfeld Gallery, The Museum at F.I.T., The Museum of Contemporary Art, Los Angeles (1988, 1992), Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, Neuberger Museum SUNY, Purchase, The New Museum (1994), New York Public Library, NYU Tisch School of Arts, Pace Gallery (1989, 2016, 2017), Paula Cooper Gallery, Peter Freeman, Inc., and Rutgers Institute for Women and Art.
  - S, 1995 -2016 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 4)
    Includes material from multiple artists shows at the following museums and galleries: University of Saint Joseph Art Gallery, Sandra Gering Gallery, The Sculpture Center, Sean Kelly Gallery, Senior and Shopmaker Gallery, SITE Santa Fe, The Socrates Sculpture Park, Sonnabend Gallery, Sperone/Westwater Gallery, Susan Sheehan Gallery, and Susan Teller Gallery. Also includes a 2006 exhibition price list for Susan Teller Gallery exhibition Under the Influence: American Artists Look at Picasso, and a 2005 exhibition price list for Susan Teller Gallery exhibition Artists of the League.
  - Smithsonian Institution, 1992-2016 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 5)
    Includes material from multiple artists shows at the Smithsonian Institution, including at The Cooper-Hewitt National Design Museum, The Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden, and The National Museum of the American Indian.
  - T, 2005-2015 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 6)
    Includes material from multiple artists shows at the following museums and galleries: Talley Dunn Gallery, The Taubman Residence, Tibor de Nagy Gallery, and Tony Shafrazi Gallery.
  - U, 1992-2015 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 7)
    Includes material from multiple artists shows at the following museums and galleries: UB Anderson Gallery at University of Buffalo, UBS Art Gallery, and the United Nations Environment Programme.
  - V, 2013-2015 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 8)
    Includes material from multiple artists shows at the following museums and galleries: Van Doren Waxter Gallery and Visionaire Gallery.
  - W, 1993-2016 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 9)
    Includes material from multiple artists shows at the following museums and galleries: The Walker Art Center, The Miriam and Ira D. Wallach Art Gallery at Columbia University, The Whitney Museum of American Art, and The Wolk Gallery at M.I.T. School of Architecture and Planning.
  - Y-Z, 2005-2015 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 10)